A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the Vice President, Media Projects, Office Files of Andrea L. Taylor FA684
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Changing Relations Project, America Becoming Documentary, 1983-1991; 4; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - Meeting in Houston, Texas, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 324-325)
  - Papers Presented at the Changing Relations Project Conference in Philadelphia, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 326)
  - Project Meeting, 1989 June (Box 26, Folder 327)
  - Meeting in Santa Monica, California, 1990 July (Box 26, Folder 328)
  - Official English Movement in Florida, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 329)
  - Meeting in Philadelphia, 1988 October (Box 26, Folder 330)
  - Santiestevan Associates Memo of Agreement, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 331)
  - WETA Suggested News Release, Revisions, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 332)
  - Niara Sudarkasa, 1983-1990 (Box 26, Folder 333)
  - Working English Video Series, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 334)
  - WETA News Release, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 335)
  - Recommendation for Grant Action Document and Grant-Related Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 336)
  - Project Board Meeting Information, Reports, and Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 337)
  - Project Statement, undated (Box 27, Folder 338)
  - Project Board Final Report, 1991 October (Box 27, Folder 339)
- Media Projects, 1971-1999; 5; 15 Cubic Feet 39 letter document boxes and 1 half-box
  The series contains correspondence with grantees and prospective grantees, invitations to seminars and conferences, articles and reports sent to Andrea Taylor, Ford Foundation press releases, promotional mail, invitations to film screenings, meeting materials, and trip files. The files pertain to documentaries, film projects, film festivals, updates from media grantmakers, public radio programs, public broadcasting, public policy initiatives, Black media, race relations, diversity initiatives, media portrayal of HIV/AIDS, women in media, Native American films, and issues in journalism.
  - Work Trips - Honolulu, Budapest, Vienna, London, and Paris, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - National Latino Communication Center - The Story of the Chicano Civil Rights Movement film, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - AIDS Media Funding, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 84-85, Box 7, Folder 86-87)
    Conference and press planning, film (PBS programming, Stand and Deliver) and other grant-related correspondence, grant action forms, reports, etc.
  - National Museum of the American Indian, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Race, Politics, and the Press, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Race Relations/Campus Diversity, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - World YWCA, Elaine J. Carlson, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - National-Community AIDS Partnership, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 92-93)
  - National-Community AIDS Partnership - NYC AIDS Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - National-Community AIDS Partnership - AIDS and Public Policy, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - National-Community AIDS Partnership - Scientist's Institute for Public Information (SIPI), 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Adair and Armstrong - "Absolutely Positive", 1989 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - AIDS Line Newsletter, Volume 1, No. 4, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - AIDSFilms, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - AIDSFilms Meeting, 1990 June (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - AIDS Prevention and Service Project, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - AmFar (American Foundation for AIDS Research), 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - AIDS Media Task Force - Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - AIDS Media Task Force - Benton Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Letter to Marc Zegans, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Doonesbury on AIDS, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Funders concerned about AIDS, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Human Rights and Social Justice, 1990-1991 Budget, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - The National Community AIDS Partnership, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - AIDS - Gannett Foundation Seminar Invitation, 1990 March (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Media Task Force, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - AmFar (American Foundation for AIDS Research) - Education Advisory Committee Meeting, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Films on Public Service and Foreign Service, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - PBS Proposal - One Border, Two Worlds, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - PBS Inside Story Series, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Nexus Television Limited - Tribes on the Frontline, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Meridian Productions, Inc. - Polish Democracy Project, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - American Cinematheque, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - APRN (Alaska Public Radio) - National Native News, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Dow Jones Newspaper Fund, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - Independent Feature Film Market, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - TV/Radio Broadcast - Four Voices: Stories of Community Based Education and Corridos! Tales of Passion and Revolution, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - WHBQ-TV - Free the Children: Breaking the Cycle of Poverty, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Jane Morrison Memorial Fund, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - WNYC Correspondence, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - WGBH - Inside Gorbachev's USSR - Guest List, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - Reviews for Inside Gorbachev's USSR, 1990 May (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - South Africa NOW, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - WGBH - Throwaway People, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Hedrick Smith - WGBH Premiere, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 185)
  - WETA Correspondence, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - WETA - Making Sense of the Sixties, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - WETA - Argentina: The Struggle and the Promise, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - WETA - Arab and Jew: Wounded Spirits in a Promised Land, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Media Listing, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - New York Council for the Humanities (Films in the Humanities), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 191)
  - The Media Institute - Hispanic Media Center, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - WNET Bill Moyers – Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - WNET Report on High Definition Television, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - WNET Metroline, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 195)
  - WNET/13 Votar/Let's Vote, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - WNET Japan: Toward the 21st Century, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 197)
  - WNET/Thirteen Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 198)
  - WNET The Eleventh Hour, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - WNET Communist Worlds, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Africa: Competing for News in the 90s, Nieman Foundation at Harvard University and the African-American Institute, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - Afro-Americans and the Evolution of a Living Constitution Radio Series: Report Brief (Mark Lloyd) (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Advocacy Institute, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - "A Case of Torture" Documentary Film, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - The Joan Shorenstein Barone Center on the Press, Politics, and Public Policy, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - The Joan Shorenstein Barone Center on the Press, Politics, and Public Policy - Meeting, 1990 June 11 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - The Joan Shorenstein Barone Center - Race, Press, and Politics Project, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Atlanta Neighborhood Housing, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Ford Foundation Bangladesh Office Video Project, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - National Academy of Sciences Status of Black Americans Project, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - USIAP Media Initiative - Tony Batten Productions, Inc., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Association for the Care of Children's Health, Beverly Johnson, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 212)
  - City of New York - Human Resources Administration - Barbara Sabol, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 213)
  - Citywide Adolescent Network Council, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 214)
  - Children Now - Correspondence with James P. Steyer, President, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 215)
  - Learning Designs - (Behind-the-Scenes) (13-Part Series on the Arts for Children), 1989 (Box 16, Folder 216)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York - Conference on Czechoslovakia, 1989 December (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - Central Independent Television, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 218)
  - Center for Media and Values, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 219)
  - Center for Communication, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 220)
  - John L. Moore (Artist), 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 221)
  - African-American Media Center - Correspondence with Gail P. Christian, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 222)
  - National Black Programming Consortium - Correspondence with Mable Haddock, Executive Director, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 223)
  - National Black Archives of Film and Broadcasting, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 224)
  - The Africa in the Americas Media Project - Correspondence with St. Clair Bourne, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 225)
  - Aviva Films New York - Correspondence with Aviva Slesin, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 226)
  - Appalshop Seedtime on the Cumberland, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 227)
  - The Chelsea Project, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 228)
  - Alive from Off Center (Rockefeller Foundation), 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 229)
  - WVTS/Detroit Who Killed Vincent Chin, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 230)
  - Public Television Programming Pipeline Notebook, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Rights and Social Justice Program Review, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - Jane Balfour Films: Autumn 1994 Nonfiction Catalogue (Box 17, Folder 233)
  - The Black Press: Soldiers Without Swords, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 234)
  - Voice of Egypt: the Life and Times of Umm Kulthum Film Project, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 235)
  - Issues Relative to Work in Media - Lynne Walker, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 236)
  - New York Observer Clipping - Rebuffed by PBS, Producers Try D.I.Y With New Hunter-Gault Rights Series, 1993 April 12 (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Media Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 238)
  - Media and Public Policy Clippings, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 239)
  - Public Television: Panacea, Pork Barrel or Public Trust? By Marilyn Lashley, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 240)
  - Pacifica Radio, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 241)
  - Pacific News Service, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 242)
  - Program Officer Orientation, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 243)
  - Office of Communications (Admin), 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Letter of Agreement with Modern Talking Picture Service - Innovating America, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Modern Talking Picture Service Invoices, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 246)
  - Richard Wright Draft Treatment with Script, Madison D. Lacy, Jr. and Kwyn D. Bader, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Moral Profiles - American Lives (Robert Coles), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 248)
  - Globalization of Mass Media, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Television Trust for the Environment (TVE) - Correspondence with Robert Lamb, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - A World of Difference Public Service Campaign, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 251)
  - ScienceWorks - Correspondence with Laurie Kreindler, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - George Mason University - Conference on Conflict Resolution in the Media, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 253)
  - The Ford Foundation - Program-Related Investments Borrower Survey Final Report, Venzen Ross Consulting, 1995 October (Box 19, Folder 254)
  - Asia Regional Meeting, Philippines, Background Reading, 1996 January 14-16 (Box 19, Folder 255)
  - Proposal to Establish the Children's Information Trust, 1995 August (Box 19, Folder 256)
  - Cultural Environment Movement, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 257)
  - West Glen Communications Press Kit, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 258)
  - Judge Baker Children's Center - Media Center for Children - Willoughby's Wonders, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 259)
  - Japan Network Group, Inc. Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 260)
  - Adham Center for Television Journalism, American University in Cairo, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 261)
  - Grantmakers in Film, Television, and Video Annual Conference, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 262)
  - Beyond Blame: Challenging Violence in the Media, Center for Media Literacy, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 263)
  - America's Children and the Information Superhighway Symposium, The Children's Partnership and the Annenberg Washington Program, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 264)
  - Letter from Lael Stegall, Social Change International, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 265)
  - Education that Works: An Action Plan for the Education of Minorities, Quality Education for Minorities Project, 1990 January (Box 20, Folder 266)
  - New York Festivals, 1995 Awards Competitions for Television Programming and Promotion Non-Broadcast Film and Video (Box 20, Folder 267)
  - International Relations Research and Training Delegation From the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 268)
  - Third World Seminar, PBS, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 269)
  - 1992 Ford Foundation Program Reviews (Box 20, Folder 270)
  - Information Paper - Cable Television, Ford Foundation, 1971 September (Box 21, Folder 271)
  - Appropriation for Office Program 1975 Printouts - Office of Communications and Office of Public Broadcasting, undated (Box 21, Folder 272)
  - Information Paper - Beyond Public Broadcasting: What Priorities in Communications for the Ford Foundation, 1973 December (Box 21, Folder 273)
  - Information Paper - Public Broadcasting and Communications, 1971 December (Box 21, Folder 274)
  - Memo from Nancy Boggs to Brock Brower Regarding Film and Television and the Ford Foundation, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 275)
  - Africana Studies Outside the United States - Africa, Brazil, the Caribbean: A Report to the Ford Foundation, 1990 March (Box 21, Folder 276)
  - Deep Dish TV Network, Benton Foundation Public Policy Initiative, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 277)
  - Tejas Newspapers, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 278)
  - What Color is the News? An Ethnic Content Analysis of Bay Area News Media, Erna Smith, 1991 December (Box 21, Folder 279)
  - Distribution of Franklin Thomas's Speeches, 1984-1991 (Box 21, Folder 280)
  - Fund for the City of New York - Public Service Awards, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 281)
  - Black Business Listing and Information - Black History Makers Awards, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 282)
  - Institute for Journalism Education, 1988-1993 (Box 21, Folder 283)
  - Independent Television Service, 1990-1994 (Box 22, Folder 284)
  - Vienna Human Rights Conference, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 285)
  - Special Report: Hispanic Broadcasting and Cable, 1993 November 15 (Box 22, Folder 286)
  - List of Grantmakers in the Arts, undated (Box 22, Folder 287)
  - Harvard University - Projects and Conferences - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 288)
  - Haiti Proposals, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 289)
  - Foundation for Independent Video and Film, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 290)
  - Dissemination of Ford Foundation Films, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 291)
  - First Edition, PBS Show, Stu Heller, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 292)
  - FemPress Proposal, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 293)
  - Hawaii International Film Festival Curriculum Guide, Grades 9-12 - When Strangers Meet, 1990 November (Box 22, Folder 294)
  - Education in International Affairs, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 295)
  - Discovery Communications, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 296)
  - Children Now, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 297)
  - Cinemaya: The Asian Film Quarterly, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 298)
  - Child Welfare League of America Publications, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 299)
  - Inter Press Service International Conference on Population and Development Proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 300)
  - Voice of America Television News Production Workshop for African Journalists at Southern Illinois University, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 301)
  - Foundation for Independent Video and Film and Thirteen-WNET, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 302)
  - Talking to Themselves: The Search for Rights and Responsibilities of the Press and Mass Media in Four Latin American Nations, Craufurd D. Goodwin and Michael Nacht, undated (Box 23, Folder 303)
  - Materials Related to Rap Artists in Brazil, Geledes-Institute of Black Women, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 304)
  - IPS Inter Press Service News Agency Correspondence, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 305)
  - WTTW/Chicago - 1993 Press and Media Profile, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 306)
  - General Interview Requests, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 307)
  - The Chicago Community Trust Annual Report Fiscal Year 1993 (Box 23, Folder 308)
  - Editorial Consultants, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - MacArthur Foundation Network Advisory Meeting, 1990 May (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - Alternative Network Meeting, MacArthur Foundation, Chicago, 1990 June (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - The WNYC Communications Group - "In the Mix", 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - The Complete Guide to Getting a Grant: How to Turn Your Ideas into Dollars, Unedited Manuscript, Laurie Blum, 1993 April (Box 24, Folder 313)
  - The Magic School Bus Fact Sheet, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 340)
  - Proposal - The Magic School Bus: A National Science Education Project from Scholastic, Inc. and Scholastic Productions, Inc., 1993 November (Box 27, Folder 341)
  - The Center for Strategic Communications Conference Directory, Chicago, 1993 March (Box 27, Folder 342)
  - Service to the Citizen Workshop Summary and Supplementary Materials, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, Sid Verba, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 343, Box 28, Folder 344)
  - Panos Institute - Conferences on African Press and Background Materials, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 345)
  - The Good Fight: The Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War Video by Sam Sills Background Info, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 346)
  - Fiscal Year 1990 Media Fund Activities, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 347)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation - Media Press Releases and Memos, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 348)
  - The Civil Rights Lawyers Documentary Project, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 349)
  - Correspondence Regarding Media Project Proposals, 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 350, Box 29, Folder 351)
  - NPR - Notes, Memos, Correspondence, and Publications, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 352)
  - NPR - Meeting with National Public Radio President and Vice Presidents, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 353)
  - NPR - Pamphlets, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 354)
  - NPR - News Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 355)
  - NPR - Grants from Ford, 1986-1991 (Box 29, Folder 356)
  - NPR - The NPR Cassette Catalog, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 357)
  - NPR - Audience Measures and Comparative Data, 1989 November (Box 29, Folder 358)
  - NPR - Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 359)
  - NPR - Fiscal Year 1990 (Box 29, Folder 360)
  - NPR - Ford Fundation Funding Credits - Eastern European Coverage, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 361)
  - NPR - John Hockenberry Proposal for Field Equipment Upgrade, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 362)
  - NPR - International Coverage, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 363)
  - NPR - News Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 364)
  - NPR - The People and the Press: Part 5 - Poll Printout, undated (Box 30, Folder 365)
  - NPR - Sustaining Fund for News Excellence, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 366)
  - NPR - Strategic Plan, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 367)
  - NPR - Training Program Proposal, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 368)
  - NPR - Annual Reports 1986, 1988, and 1991, 1986-1991 (Box 30, Folder 369)
  - 1890 Land Grant Universities Film Project, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 370)
  - ACCION International and Coastal Enterprises (CEI) - PRI Borrowers, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 371)
  - Ad-Net, Win Roll, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 372)
  - Instituto de Pesquisas das Culturas Negras (IPCN) and the Brazil Network, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 373)
  - Alyce and Topper Carew: Rainbow TV Works, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 374)
  - American Association of Fund-Raising Counsel, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 375)
  - American Civil Liberties Union AIDS Project, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 376)
  - American Dream, Barbara Kopple Documentary, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 377)
  - American Democracy in Crisis, Center for Investigative Reporting, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 378)
  - The Role of Arms Control in Assuring Security in Europe, undated (Box 30, Folder 379)
  - A Tiempo - University of Texas at Austin Radio Series, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 380)
  - Caribbean Film Institute, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 381)
  - "Caribbean Screenplay", BBC and International Broadcasting Trust and "Shacking Up," Afravision and International Broadasting Trust, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 382)
  - Caribe: The Island World, International Cinema, Inc., 1987 (Box 31, Folder 383)
  - Center for National Independence in Politics - Project Vote Smart, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 384)
  - Center for Visual History: The American Cinema Project, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 385)
  - Challenge to America: Janet Lustig and Hedrick Smith, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 386)
  - Child Survival and Reproductive Health, The Family House, Public Health Soap Opera, Dr. Farag Elkamel, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 387)
  - Race, Politics and the Press, Ellen Hume, Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 388)
  - International Media Resource Exchange, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 389)
  - International Centre for Ethnic Studies (Sri Lanka, Ireland and Cyprus), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 390)
  - In Small Places, 40th Anniversary of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, Chuck Olin, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 391)
  - In the Name of Love, Domestic Violence Film, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 392)
  - In the Shadow of Love: A Teen's AIDS Story, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 393)
  - Letter from Vincent G. Harding, Iliff School of Theology, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 394)
  - Horizon Communications - One Second Before Sunrise, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 395)
  - Harding, Vincent - Center for the Study of Religion and Democratic Renewal - Gandhi, Hamer, King Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 396)
  - H-2 Worker Film Proposal, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 397)
  - Great Performances "A Bowl of Beings," Moctesuma Esparza, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 398)
  - Film News Now Foundation, Grant Number 905-1517, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 399)
  - Farming America, Hudson River Film and Video, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 400)
  - To Render a Life or to Change the World Conference, Duke University, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 401)
  - Don Connors Productions, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 402)
  - Institute of the Americas Drug Abuse Project, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 403)
  - Doing the Right Thing: Minorities in the Communications Industries, Center for Communication Conference, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 404)
  - Dade Community Foundation 1991 Annual Report (Box 31, Folder 405)
  - Crossroads: Vivian Kleiman Productions, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 406)
  - The Washington Report on the Hemisphere, Council on Hemispheric Affairs, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 407)
  - Mama's Pushcarts, Diamond Royals Productions, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 408)
    Documentary on La Mama Experimental Theatre and Ellen Stewart
  - Is Anyone in Charge?: A Television Documentary about American Foreign Policy in the 1990s, MainStreet Media Center, 1988-1991 (Box 32, Folder 409)
  - Island Press/Smithsonian Journalism and Environment Program, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 410)
    Grant: 905-0668
  - Jamison and Leary Advertising - Case Study, Stanford University, undated (Box 32, Folder 411)
  - Karol Media, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 412)
  - Passing Thru Linden, Thomas C. Layton, Wallace Alexander Gerbode Foundation, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 413)
  - Life and Death in the Rain Forests, Robert Richter Productions, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 414)
  - Loni Ding - Color of Honor, Awards, 11th Asian American International Film Festival, 1987-1989 (Box 32, Folder 415)
  - Excellence in the Public Sector, Martin Sandler Productions, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 416)
  - M. Booth and Associates - Symposium Honoring 1991 Charles A. Dana Award for Pioneering Achievements in Health and Education Winners (Box 32, Folder 417)
  - NCAP: National Community AIDS Partnership - Communication Audit, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 418)
  - National Association of Negro Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 419)